A Guide to the Hugh L. Robertson Collection, 1948-1983
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Series 3, Negatives, 1948-1959
  - Sub-series 3-3: Family Life, Undated
    - Hugh L. Robertson, family life at 6907 Pine Crest Avenue, McLean, Va. (3 images), Undated (Box 5, Folder 257)
    - Hugh L. Robertson, family life at 6907 Pine Crest Avenue, McLean, Va. (3 images), Undated (Box 5, Folder 258)
    - Hugh L. Robertson, family life at 6907 Pine Crest Avenue, McLean, Va. (3 images), Undated (Box 5, Folder 259)
    - Hugh L. Robertson, family life at 6907 Pine Crest Avenue, McLean, Va. (3 images), Undated (Box 5, Folder 260)
    - Hugh L. Robertson, family life at 6907 Pine Crest Avenue, McLean, Va. (3 images), Undated (Box 5, Folder 261)
    - Hugh L. Robertson, family life at 6907 Pine Crest Avenue, McLean, Va. (3 images), Undated (Box 5, Folder 262)
    - Hugh L. Robertson, family life at 6907 Pine Crest Avenue, McLean, Va. (3 images), Undated (Box 5, Folder 263)
    - Hugh L. Robertson, family life at 6907 Pine Crest Avenue, McLean, Va. (3 images), Undated (Box 5, Folder 264)
    - Hugh L. Robertson, portrait, Undated (Box 5, Folder 265)
    - Hugh L. Robertson, portrait, c. 1959 (Box 5, Folder 266)
  - Sub-series 3-4: Post-World War II Asia, Undated
    - Japan, children gathered in the street, Undated (Box 5, Folder 267)
    - Japan, exterior of government building, Undated (Box 5, Folder 268)
    - Japan, PMC locomotive in train yard, Undated (Box 5, Folder 269)
    - Japan, Shonan Girls High School, Undated (Box 5, Folder 270)
    - Japan, street scene, Undated (Box 5, Folder 271)
    - Japan, woman holding baby in a store front doorway, Undated (Box 5, Folder 272)
    - Japan, young boy sitting on stairway, Undated (Box 5, Folder 273)
    - Japan, young boy sitting on stairway, Undated (Box 5, Folder 274)
  - Sub-series 3-5: Unidentified, 1956, Undated
    - Great Lakes Ceramic Exhibition 1956 Awardees, Betty J. Rider and two unknown women posing with certificates and their sculptures, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 275)
    - Unidentified farm (McLean?), barn and a field of stacks of wheat [2 negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 276)
    - Unidentified farm (McLean?), barn and a field of stacks of wheat [2 negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 277)
    - Unidentified farm (McLean?), barn and a field of stacks of wheat [2 negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 278)
    - Unidentified farm (McLean?), barn and a field of stacks of wheat [2 negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 279)
    - Unidentified, appliance store, window display promoting the Easy Spindrier washing machine [2 negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 280)
    - Unidentified, baby on a couch, Undated (Box 5, Folder 281)
    - Unidentified, church, interior view of wedding, Undated (Box 5, Folder 282)
    - Unidentified, church, view of bell tower, Undated (Box 5, Folder 283)
    - Unidentified, church, view of exterior rotunda, Undated (Box 5, Folder 284)
    - Unidentified, couple cutting cake, Undated (Box 5, Folder 285)
    - Unidentified, crying boy getting his hair cut by barber, Undated (Box 5, Folder 286)
    - Unidentified, dead man lying in a flag draped casket, Undated (Box 5, Folder 287)
    - Unidentified, dead man lying in a flag draped casket, Undated (Box 5, Folder 288)
    - Unidentified, dead man lying in a flag draped casket, Undated (Box 5, Folder 289)
    - Unidentified, group posing at a dance, Undated (Box 5, Folder 290)
    - Unidentified, man and woman walking down a hallway, Undated (Box 5, Folder 291)
    - Unidentified, man riding a horse (McLean?), Undated (Box 5, Folder 292)
    - Unidentified, man riding a horse (McLean?), Undated (Box 5, Folder 293)
    - Unidentified, portrait of a man, Undated (Box 5, Folder 294)
    - Unidentified, portrait of a man [5 negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 295)
    - Unidentified, portrait of a woman [2 color negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 296)
    - Unidentified, portrait of a woman [2 negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 297)
    - Unidentified, portrait of a woman [3 color negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 298)
    - Unidentified, portrait of a woman [3 negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 299)
    - Unidentified, portrait of a woman [3 negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 300)
    - Unidentified, portrait of a woman [4 color negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 301)
    - Unidentified, portrait of a woman [4 negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 302)
    - Unidentified, portrait of a woman [6 negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 303)
    - Unidentified, portrait of a woman [6 negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 304)
    - Unidentified, portrait of a woman [color negative], Undated (Box 5, Folder 305)
    - Unidentified, portrait of a woman and young girl [2 negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 306)
    - Unidentified, portrait of a woman, Peggy Lawrence or possibly "Mac" McGinley's daughter [6 negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 307)
    - Unidentified, portrait of a young girl [6 negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 308)
    - Unidentified, portrait of an older couple, Undated (Box 5, Folder 309)
    - Unidentified, portrait of an older man [4 negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 310)
    - Unidentified, portrait of an older woman [3 negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 311)
    - Unidentified, portrait of baby, Undated (Box 5, Folder 312)
    - Unidentified, portrait of couple [6 negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 313)
    - Unidentified, portrait of couple and child, Undated (Box 5, Folder 314)
    - Unidentified, portrait of couple with young girl [6 negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 315)
    - Unidentified, portrait of three young boys [6 negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 316)
    - Unidentified, portrait of two young boys [5 negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 317)
    - Unidentified, portrait of two young boys and a baby [3 negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 318)
    - Unidentified, portrait of woman with two young boys [6 negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 319)